{
    "id": "d84bbaca542048959a8ec66cefbb4fa1",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He asked me …………………. I would like to accompany him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1bf222a921f54eaa90fb92dd82acd42f"
        },
        {
            "question": "James ran very fast ………………….. he could not catch up with Mike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "yet",
                "still",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "417e514c9b89487496603ee60453e240"
        },
        {
            "question": "Two ……………….. two make four.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "also",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1eaaa4ac414b41219fa6ad04055bb45b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I work hard ………………. I may pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "and",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b54729edb9d41ae9ebcd891888f8265"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you work hard, you will pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whether",
                "If",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "831a96c1e49c4cf6a62ce2d00bbc0996"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is older ………………… her husband.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7aeb4b959e754c25907229e49b63d4e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "They left the town …………………. the epidemic had spread there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "while",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f9185cbb2354fa897bacc3103cbf46e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Go ………………. you like.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "where",
                "whence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9c6d8afe8ed457f88493c6027f8a924"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither a borrower ........................ a lender be.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nor",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "996b3a06b1ea49bbaf519580e81abdf4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look ...................... you leap.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "while",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "46fa918094684004b76b588d5d918451"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me ..................... I wanted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ed539f1fa7964ff995c3e18ab4ac776b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been a long time ......................... I last met him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4fecbe29cde44546b116cdd193bd11fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... you focus on your work, you will not succeed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11295f5d0ee24377818c395ab19de82c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We eat ........................... we may live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "what",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f86d060a352546c59442e67b3fd2518f"
        }
    ]
}